

Objective

Find a job in a professional environment, respect each other and take advantage of programming experience. Try to learning as much as possible and doing my best in order to accompish my task. From that, develop my skills with development of company.

Education

Cao Thang Technical College [September 2014 - October 2017]

Major: Information Technology

GPA:6.76/10 with Final Project:8.5/10

Work experience

Commercial Website (ASP.NET & MS SQL SERVER)
[January 2016 - May 2016]

Wine Store Management(.NET winform & MS SQL SERVER) [October 2016 - December 2016]

Key Skill and strengths

- Quick learner
- Good communication and interpersonal skills
- Good in analytical skills
- Good teamwork, Friendly

Contact information

October 23, 1996 0902771783 thongvo2310@gmail.com 304/35B Pham The Hien Street, Ward 3, District 8, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

Skills

C#
SQL Server
HTML + CSS
PHP
Teamwork
Independent
Public Speaking

Interests

Soccer Watching movie
Game Music